

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and n nhỏ để hỗ trợ tiền host và lưu lượng truy cập hàng tháng cho trang web. Không có giới hạn mức đ of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

# **EDUCATION**



#### FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. CICERO HEDONIST ROOTS Until recently, the prevailing view assumed lor administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

## **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ly unchanged except for an o and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to Sell My Personal Information · Change Consent Հայերեն Shqip Българ goods in and out العربية
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

**Recognition and Gains:** 

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

# **CVPRO JSC**Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer Iso of those who resist. Now a pure snore disturbeded sum du' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US efor

# **REFERENCES**



# **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

### **SKILLS**





# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt Idus PageMaker including versions of Lorem and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities